It is with Ajay
and Gupta ji how are you come come come come come
I am fine after the long gown now at last the
business is back on track ok give
me plus 2 minutes this is my home loan
on my online today the due date just
fill it Michael it doesn't matter
my daughter's wedding is on 10th take your measurements and get a
suit ready for me ok I will
make the suit but Dubey ji this suit is yours, I will
give it on 11th instead of 10th you are
talking here Gupta if it gets torn then it is on 10th
what will I do with this drying after that the suit will become useless yes so in the same way
home loan earnings also have to be
paid on the due date not after that otherwise
your credit score and name earned over the years will get
spoiled and getting a loan in future will
also become difficult understand pay
attention to repaying home loan on due date this is the
sign of wisdom